
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question:"Solve the equation for x: 3x - 8 = 16",
    answer: "8",
    options: [
      "5",
      "9",
      "2",
      "7"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: " If 2x + 5 = 17, find the value of x.",
    answer: "7",
    options: [
      "8",
      "2",
      "4",
      "7"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Solve the inequality: 2x + 3 < 11",
    answer: "8",
    options: [
      "8",
      "9",
      "10",
      "11"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Solve the inequality: 4x - 7 > 25",
    answer: "x > 8",
    options: [
      "x > 4",
      "x > 5",
      "x > 7",
      "x > 6"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Solve the quadratic equation: x^2 - 5x + 6 = 0",
    answer: "x = 2, x = 3",
    options: [
      "x = 2, x = 3",
      "x = 2, x = 8",
      "x = 2, x = 7",
      "x = 2, x = 5"
    ]
  },
  

     {
   numb: 6,
   question: "Solve the quadratic equation: 2x^2 - 7x + 3 = 0",
    answer: "x = 1/2, x = 3",
    options: [
      "x = 1/2, x = 3",
      "x = 1/3, x = 1",
      "x = 1/5, x = 6",
      "x = 1/2, x = 4"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Solve the equation for y: 4y + 9 = 25",
     answer: "4",
     options: [
       "5",
       "2",
       "2",
       "4"
     ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "If 3y - 8 = 10, find the value of y.",
       answer:"6",
       options: [
         "4" ,
         "5",
         "6",
         "7"
       ]
      },
      {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Solve the inequality: 3y - 5 ≤ 16",
         answer: "y ≤ 7",
         options: [
           "y ≤ 3",
           "y ≤ 2",
           "y ≤ 2",
           "y ≤ 78"
         ]
        },
        {
          numb: 10,
          question: " Solve the inequality: 5y + 4 ≥ 24",
          answer: "y ≤ 7",
          options: [
            "y ≤ 3",
            "y ≤ 2",
            "y ≤ 2",
            "y ≤ 78"
          ]
          }
];